Hello friends, welcome.
ICICI Lombard has declared its quarterly
results. So today we will do a
full analysis of the results.
First, we will look at the company's results.
Second, the company's share rolling pattern and
other fundamentals of the company. Third, we will
check the valuation. Whether it is overpriced or
underpriced. And finally, we are going to
discuss whether we should buy
new shares in it or if you already
have these shares, what should you do? Should you
hold them or
should you sell and exit? So, stay tuned to
this video from beginning to end. The
total number on this is the company's overall
4500 crores and last year onwards it is around 3800 crores. This is
18% less than last year.
We are seeing growth in cotton.
Friends, if I talk about net profit,
it has increased from 40046 crores to ₹590 crores. So,
this is 32%, we are
seeing growth in the company. And
if you look at cotton cotton also,  If you see, it was worth 3
1/2 crores in the new cofit in June 2022
and it has increased from that to ₹590, so
we are getting to see very good results of the company, so friends,
if you look at the net off margin of the company, then the
net off margin of the company in the last quarter is
very good, Arun Napunji said 13%
and last year it was around 12%, so
overall the total income of the company has
also
increased significantly and the results that
we are seeing here in the company's fever, if we
talk about the pattern, then here the
company has a holding of 48%, the same fee, if we are
decreasing our holding in shares, then
earlier it was 28%, now it has become around 25%
and we are
increasing our holding in it, so it has
increased from 13% to around 15%
and friends, if I look at its financials  If I
talk about this company's
sales here, if you study the sales of the last 10 years, then the
sales are continuously
increasing here and here the net of profit is
also continuously increasing here,
only
if we talk about March 2021, then the net and
then the company had decreased there, but if
you look at it, then you will see that it is
expected that by March 2023 the
company's net and then it will be
around Rs 1400 crore and
apart from this, if we talk about the profit of the friends, then that
too is continuously increasing here
and
friends, the second thing if we look at its return on
capital employed, then it is 19% and the
return on equity is 15%, so on
average we can say that it is return on
capital employed and return of equity
and if we look at the valuation, then friends, its
period show is 39 and the book value is  It is
193, so friends, in valuation, if
I want to compare whether it
is overvalued or undervalued or
fairly valued, then how will we check that?
First of all, we look at peer comparison,
but in peer comparison,
mostly the peer company here is
life insurance, but here this
company is general insurance, so
according to that, friends, I will have to see its median
price, what is its median price,
so if you look at the last one year's
medium price toning, that is, the average
price, is
7.7, but the current price, that is,
its average price,
right now, it is somewhere quite, the
share price, if you have seen it from 1548,
from there Arun has fallen by 25%, so
now if I want to
invest for the long term, then
we would definitely invest in this stock,
and at which level should it be done,
I will tell you later,
friends, right now I have opened its weekly
chart here and its  The high was
around 1670 and if you
look here, then on the weekly pattern,
lower highs and lower lows are being set continuously. So
if you look here, this
level is lower again, this lower high is set again.
Here, a lower high is set and there is a
lower loss. Meaning, friends, the
trend of the stock here is quite down.
We are seeing a trend here
on a weekly basis. And friends, if
I talk about a daily basis, at
which level can we enter on a daily basis,
friends, let's discuss that too. So,
here the
moving average is coming out. If you
look at this green line, what is the van to six van
coming out? Till
when is 200 on the upper side, we are
not going to make a new entry in it. And until this 200
crosses this moving average, only then will we
take a new entry in this stock. And
when it crosses this, its first
target is coming out, Arun
of 1368 and the second target is coming out.
Friends, that and that is coming out of 1411,
so these two targets can be
seen by us on an immediate basis,
keeping the unbalanced intelligence share inside, you have purchased it
with an eye on it,
then you
can create a hold position in it again, then it will be your decision whether
you want to hold it or not,
for your new entry it will have to
cross the moving average, only then
we can make a new entry in it, so I
hope friends that you liked this video, if you liked
this video then
like this video and if you have
not subscribed to the channel yet then do subscribe
and if you have any suggestion for any
show, please do tell me in the comment box,
thank you